

## ABOUT ME

My name is Julián Yago Contreras Lucero, I am 20 years old. I am studying software development at UADE and in April 2023 I finished the Full Stack Developer Bootcamp at Soy Henry, also increasing my knowledge in programming-related courses. I seek to develop and grow in the technological field and obtain knowledge in the survey and implementation of solutions for different clients.

## CONTACT

- (54) 11 6460-2560
- jjulian.contrerass@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/juliancontre raslucero
- github.com/julcontrerass

### EDUCATION

- -2nd year in software development at Universidad Argentina De Las Empresas currently
- -Full Stack Developer in Soy Henry Finished in April 2023

## PORTFOLIO



# TECH SKILLS

#### JAVASCRIPT Y TYPESCRIPT

FRONTEND

Html5 Css3 Ajax React Js

> React Native Redux

BACKEND

NodeJs Sequelize Express Testing BASES DE DATOS

MongoDB PostgreSQL

#### SOFT SKILLS

- -Adaptability
- -Curiosity
- -Dedication
- -Empathy
- -Problem solvina
- -Negotiation
- -Cooperation

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Diaper acuarela

ENE 2021 - JUL 2021

- Seller
- Repositor
- Deliveryman

#### Sportclub belgrano

JUL 2021 - FEB 2022

- Receptionist
- Closing and cash control
- Administration

#### Sportclub obras paraguay

ABRIL 2022 - DIC 2022

- Receptionist
- Closing and cash control
- Administration

# LENGUAGES

- -Spanish
- -English B1